https://www.tapplastics.com/about/privacy

Privacy Policy
At TAP Plastics Incorporated, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you to process orders only. Please read on for more details about our privacy policy.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?
When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, phone number, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
How do we protect customer information?
When you place orders, we provide the use of a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) encrypts the information you input before it is sent to the Web server. We then retrieve all orders using an encrypted connection, ensuring the safety of your personal information. Credit card information is sent directly to the appropriate credit card company during order processing and not retained. All customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.
Will we disclose the information to outside parties?
TAP Plastics Incorporated does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. This information is for our private records only.
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by TAP Plastics Incorporated. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.
Effective June 22, 2006
How To
TAP Instructional Videos
